A Guide to the JDR 3rd Fund records FA081
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Arts in Education Program - Kathryn Bloom Files, 1967-1979; 11; 88 Cubic Feet 204 document cases
  - Arts in Education Program - Kathryn Bloom Files - Contact File, 11.C
    - Arts, Performing - Theatre - United States Institute for Theatre Technology - Membership Lists, 1969-1975 (Box 280, Folder 2060)
    - Arts, Performing - Theatre - University Resident Theatre Association (URTA) - Correspondence, 1970-1976 (Box 280, Folder 2061)
    - Arts, Performing - Theatre - University Resident Theatre Association (URTA) - Meetings, 1971-1972 (Box 280, Folder 2062)
    - Arts, Performing - Theatre - Youth Theatre Productions, 1975 (Box 280, Folder 2063)
    - Educational Institutions - Academies (A-I) (Box 280, Folder 2064)
    - Educational Institutions - Academies (J-Z) (Box 281, Folder 2065)
    - Educational Institutions - Colleges (A-C) (Box 281, Folder 2066)
    - Educational Institutions - Colleges (D-H) (Box 281, Folder 2067)
    - Educational Institutions - Colleges (I-M) (Box 281, Folder 2068)
    - Educational Institutions - Colleges (N-S) (Box 281, Folder 2069)
    - Educational Institutions - Colleges (T-Z) (Box 281, Folder 2070)
    - Educational Institutions - Schools (A-C) (Box 282, Folder 2071)
    - Educational Institutions - Schools - Detroit Institute of Arts - Correspondence, 1972-1977 (Box 282, Folder 2072)
    - Educational Institutions - Schools - Detroit Institute of Arts - Meetings, 1972-1974 (Box 282, Folder 2073)
    - Educational Institutions - Schools - Detroit Institute of Arts - Publications, 1973 (Box 282, Folder 2074)
    - Educational Institutions - Schools (D-F) (Box 282, Folder 2075)
    - Educational Institutions - Schools - Fiedel School, 1976-1977 (Box 282, Folder 2076)
    - Educational Institutions - Schools (G-H) (Box 283, Folder 2077)
    - Educational Institutions - Schools (L) (Box 283, Folder 2078)
    - Educational Institutions - Schools (M-N) (Box 283, Folder 2079)
    - Educational Institutions - Schools - Northport Union Free School District #4, 1969-1973 (Box 283, Folder 2080)
    - Educational Institutions - Schools - Northport Union Free School District #4, 1969-1973 (Box 283, Folder 2081)
    - Educational Institutions - Schools (O-R) (Box 283, Folder 2082)
    - Educational Institutions - Schools (S-Z) (Box 284, Folder 2083)
    - Educational Institutions - Universities (A-B) (Box 284, Folder 2084)
    - Educational Institutions - Universities - University of California at Los Angeles (UCLA) - Correspondence, 1968-1976 (Box 284, Folder 2085)
    - Educational Institutions - Universities - University of California at Los Angeles (UCLA) - Research Papers, 1978 (Box 284, Folder 2086)
    - Educational Institutions - Universities - University of California - Other Branches (Box 284, Folder 2087)
    - Educational Institutions - Universities (Ca-Ci) (Box 284, Folder 2088)
    - Educational Institutions - Universities - Columbia University - Correspondence, 1971-1978 (Box 284, Folder 2089)
    - Educational Institutions - Universities - Columbia University - Proposed Center for the Arts, 1971-1972 (Box 284, Folder 2090)
    - Educational Institutions - Universities - Columbia University - Proposed Center for the Arts, 1971-1972 (Box 285, Folder 2091)
    - Educational Institutions - Universities (Co-F) (Box 285, Folder 2092)
    - Educational Institutions - Universities - Georgia State University, 1972 (Box 285, Folder 2093)
    - Educational Institutions - Universities - University of Hawaii, 1967-1976 (Box 285, Folder 2094)
    - Educational Institutions - Universities - Hofstra University, 1970-1974 (Box 285, Folder 2095)
    - Educational Institutions - Universities - University of Illinois - Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box 285, Folder 2096)
    - Educational Institutions - Universities - University of Illinois - Publications, 1978 (Box 285, Folder 2097)
    - Educational Institutions - Universities - Indiana University, 1968; 1974-1975 (Box 285, Folder 2098)
    - Educational Institutions - Universities (J-L) (Box 286, Folder 2099)
    - Educational Institutions - Universities - University of Massachusetts, 1971-1974 (Box 286, Folder 2100)
    - Educational Institutions - Universities (M) (Box 286, Folder 2101)
    - Educational Institutions - Universities - University of New Mexico, 1971-1972; 1975 (Box 286, Folder 2102)
    - Educational Institutions - Universities - New York University - Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 286, Folder 2103)
    - Educational Institutions - Universities - New York University - "Educational Quarterly", 1975; 1977-1978 (Box 286, Folder 2104)
    - Educational Institutions - Universities (N-O) (Box 286, Folder 2105)
    - Educational Institutions - Universities - Pennsylvania State University, 1968-1976 (Box 287, Folder 2106)
    - Educational Institutions - Universities - Purdue University, 1971 (Box 287, Folder 2107)
    - Educational Institutions - Universities (R-Se) (Box 287, Folder 2108)
    - Educational Institutions - Universities - University of South Carolina - Symposium, March 25-27, 1974 (Box 287, Folder 2109)
    - Educational Institutions - Universities (So-St) (Box 287, Folder 2110)
    - Educational Institutions - Universities - Syracuse University, 1971-1972 (Box 287, Folder 2111)
    - Educational Institutions - Universities (T-Z) (Box 287, Folder 2112)
    - Educational Organizations - Advisory and Learning Exchange, 1975 (Box 288, Folder 2113)
    - Educational Organizations - Alliance of Associations for Advancement of Education, 1974 (Box 288, Folder 2114)
    - Educational Organizations - American Association for Higher Education, 1968-1971 (Box 288, Folder 2115)
    - Educational Organizations - Alliance of Associations for Advancement of Education, 1974 (Box 288, Folder 2116)
    - Educational Organizations - American Association of State Colleges and Universities, 1974-1976 (Box 288, Folder 2117)
    - Educational Organizations - American College Testing Program, 1976-1977 (Box 288, Folder 2118)
    - Educational Organizations - American Council on Education, 1970 (Box 288, Folder 2119)
    - Educational Organizations - American Council of Learned Societies, 1970 (Box 288, Folder 2120)
    - Educational Organizations - American Educational Research Association - Correspondence, 1970-1976 (Box 288, Folder 2121)
    - Educational Organizations - American Educational Research Association - Meeting, February 23-25, 1973 (Box 288, Folder 2122)
    - Educational Organizations - American Educational Research Association - Meeting, February 23-25, 1973 (Box 288, Folder 2123)
    - Educational Organizations - American Educational Research Association - Meeting, February 23-25, 1973 (Box 288, Folder 2124)
    - Educational Organizations - American Educational Research Association - Meeting, February 23-25, 1973 (Box 288, Folder 2125)
    - Educational Organizations - American Educational Research Association - Meetings, 1973-1976 (Box 289, Folder 2126)
    - Educational Organizations - American Educational Research Association - Meetings, 1973-1976 (Box 289, Folder 2127)
    - Educational Organizations - American Educational Research Association - Meetings, 1973-1976 (Box 289, Folder 2128)
    - Educational Organizations - American Institutes for Research, 1970-1973 (Box 289, Folder 2129)
    - Educational Organizations - Association for Supervision and Curriculum Development - Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 289, Folder 2130)
    - Educational Organizations - Association for Supervision and Curriculum Development - Meetings, 1977-1978 (Box 289, Folder 2131)
    - Educational Organizations - Carnegie Institute of Washington, 1972 (Box 290, Folder 2132)
    - Educational Organizations - Center for City Building Educational Programs, 1975 (Box 290, Folder 2133)
    - Educational Organizations - Center for Educational Leadership, 1971 (Box 290, Folder 2134)
    - Educational Organizations - Center for Visual Literacy, 1970-1971 (Box 290, Folder 2135)
    - Educational Organizations - Coalition of Adult Education Organizations, 1976-1977 (Box 290, Folder 2136)
    - Educational Organizations - Council for Basic Education, 1974-1978 (Box 290, Folder 2137)
    - Educational Organizations - Council for Educational Development, 1975 (Box 290, Folder 2138)
    - Educational Organizations - Educational Facilities Laboratories - Correspondence and Newsletters, 1968-1977 (Box 290, Folder 2139)
    - Educational Organizations - Educational Facilities Laboratories - Publications, 1970-1974 (Box 290, Folder 2140)
    - Educational Organizations - Educational Facilities Laboratories - Publications, 1970-1974 (Box 290, Folder 2141)
    - Educational Organizations - Educational Facilities Laboratories - Publications, 1970-1974 (Box 290, Folder 2142)
    - Educational Organizations - Educational Facilities Laboratories - Publications, 1975-1976 (Box 291, Folder 2143)
    - Educational Organizations - Educational Facilities Laboratories - Working Papers, 1972-1973 (Box 291, Folder 2144)
    - Educational Organizations - Educational Testing Service - Correspondence and Newsletters, 1973-1978 (Box 291, Folder 2145)
    - Educational Organizations - Educational Testing Service - Meeting, September 24-26, 1978 (Box 291, Folder 2146)
    - Educational Organizations - Evaluation Network, 1976-1978 (Box 291, Folder 2147)
    - Educational Organizations - Far West Laboratory, 1976 (Box 292, Folder 2148)
    - Educational Organizations - Florida Educational Research Association, 1975-1976 (Box 292, Folder 2149)
    - Educational Organizations - Global Perspectives in Education, 1977 (Box 292, Folder 2150)
    - Educational Organizations - Heuristics, Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 292, Folder 2151)
    - Educational Organizations - Institute of International Education, 1970-1976 (Box 292, Folder 2152)
    - Educational Organizations - Institute for Services to Education, 1976 (Box 292, Folder 2153)
    - Educational Organizations - National Association of Elementary School Principals - Meeting, April 27-28, 1976 (Box 292, Folder 2154)
    - Educational Organizations - National Association of Elementary School Principals - Publications, 1971-1978 (Box 292, Folder 2155)
    - Educational Organizations - National Association of Elementary School Principals - Publications, 1971-1978 (Box 292, Folder 2156)
    - Educational Organizations - National Association of Elementary School Principals - Publications, 1971-1978 (Box 292, Folder 2157)
    - Educational Organizations - National Association of School Councelors, 1977 (Box 293, Folder 2158)
    - Educational Organizations - National Center for Educational Brokering, 1976-1977 (Box 293, Folder 2159)
    - Educational Organizations - National Commission on Resources for Youth, 1974 (Box 293, Folder 2160)
    - Educational Organizations - National Council on Teachers of English, 1978-1979 (Box 293, Folder 2161)
    - Educational Organizations - National Education Association, 1963; 1970-1976 (Box 293, Folder 2162)
    - Educational Organizations - National Humanities Faculty, 1969; 1973-1977 (Box 293, Folder 2163)
    - Educational Organizations - Northwest Educational Regional Laboratory, 1974 (Box 293, Folder 2164)
    - Educational Organizations - San Francisco Consortium, 1975 (Box 293, Folder 2165)
    - Educational Organizations - Social Science Education Consortium, 1973-1974 (Box 293, Folder 2166)
    - Educational Organizations - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1968 (Box 293, Folder 2167)
    - Educational Organizations - Southwest Educational Development Laboratory, 1971-1972 (Box 294, Folder 2168)
    - Educational Organizations - Students International Meditation Society, 1972 (Box 294, Folder 2169)
    - Educational Organizations - Teachers and Writers Collaborative, 1975 (Box 294, Folder 2170)
    - Foundations - A. Philip Randolph Educational Foundation, 1973 (Box 294, Folder 2171)
    - Foundations - Agricultural Development Council, 1973 (Box 294, Folder 2172)
    - Foundations - Carnegie Corporation, 1970-1978 (Box 294, Folder 2173)
    - Foundations - Charles Stewart Mott Foundation, 1978 (Box 294, Folder 2174)
    - Foundations - Council on Foundations - Brochures, 1971-1978 (Box 294, Folder 2175)
    - Foundations - Council on Foundations - Correspondence, 1968-1979 (Box 294, Folder 2176)
    - Foundations - Council on Foundations - Correspondence, 1968-1979 (Box 294, Folder 2177)
    - Foundations - Council on Foundations - "Foundation News", 1973-1976 (Box 294, Folder 2178)
    - Foundations - Danforth Foundation, 1974-1979 (Box 295, Folder 2179)
    - Foundations - Earl Rowland Foundation, 1973 (Box 295, Folder 2180)
    - Foundations - Filer Commission, 1975 (Box 295, Folder 2181)
    - Foundations - Floyd Foundation, 1974 (Box 295, Folder 2182)
    - Foundations - Ford Foundation - Brochures, 1970-1974 (Box 295, Folder 2183)
    - Foundations - Ford Foundation - Correspondence, 1969-1976 (Box 295, Folder 2184)
    - Foundations - Ford Foundation - "Letter", 1973; 1975-1978 (Box 295, Folder 2185)
    - Foundations - Genessee Valley Arts Foundation, 1973 (Box 295, Folder 2186)
    - Foundations - Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1972-1975 (Box 295, Folder 2187)
    - Foundations - Gund Foundation, 1977 (Box 295, Folder 2188)
    - Foundations - Karamu Foundation, 1972; 1974 (Box 295, Folder 2189)
    - Foundations - Kettering Foundation, 1972; 1976 (Box 296, Folder 2190)
    - Foundations - Longview Foundation, 1978 (Box 296, Folder 2191)
    - Foundations - Martha Baird Rockefeller Fund - Report, 1969-1973 (Box 296, Folder 2192)
    - Foundations - Martha Holden Jennings Foundation, 1975 (Box 296, Folder 2193)
    - Foundations - McGregor Fund - Report, 1975 (Box 296, Folder 2194)
    - Foundations - National Science Foundation, 1969-1970 (Box 296, Folder 2195)
    - Foundations - Needmoor Fund - Report, 1978 (Box 296, Folder 2196)
    - Foundations - New Haven Foundation, 1973 (Box 296, Folder 2197)
    - Foundations - Noble Foundation, 1973-1977 (Box 296, Folder 2198)
    - Foundations - Norton Simon Foundation, 1973-1974 (Box 296, Folder 2199)
    - Foundations - Performing Arts Foundation, 1970-1974 (Box 296, Folder 2200)
    - Foundations - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, 1973-1978 (Box 296, Folder 2201)
    - Foundations - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - Report, 1975 (Box 296, Folder 2202)
    - Foundations - Rosenberg Foundation - Report, 1972 (Box 296, Folder 2203)
    - Foundations - Stone Foundation, 1974 (Box 296, Folder 2204)
    - Foundations - Twentieth Century Fund, 1972; 1975 (Box 296, Folder 2205)
    - Foundations - Western States Arts Foundation, 1975-1977 (Box 296, Folder 2206)
    - Foundations - William and Flora Hewlett Foundation, 1977-1978 (Box 296, Folder 2207)
    - Institutional Development Corporation - Cities in Schools Program, 1977-1978 (Box 297, Folder 2208)
    - Junior Leagues - Correspondence, 1969-1978 (Box 297, Folder 2209)
    - Junior Leagues - Birmingham Junior League, 1974 (Box 297, Folder 2210)
    - Museums - Brochures - General, 1968-1978 (Box 297, Folder 2211)
    - Museums - Correspondence - General, 1968-1979 (Box 297, Folder 2212)
    - Museums - Correspondence - General, 1968-1979 (Box 297, Folder 2213)
    - Museums - Materials - General, 1966 (Box 297, Folder 2214)
    - Museums - Papers - General, 1966; 1970-1974 (Box 298, Folder 2215)
    - Museums - Boston Museum of Fine Arts, 1968-1971 (Box 298, Folder 2216)
    - Museums - Brooklyn Museum, 1973 (Box 298, Folder 2217)
    - Museums - Carnegie Institute, 1976-1978 (Box 298, Folder 2218)
    - Museums - Cleveland Museum of Art, 1970-1972 (Box 298, Folder 2219)
    - Museums - Columbus Gallery of Fine Arts, 1975 (Box 298, Folder 2220)
    - Museums - De Cordova Museum, 1975-1976 (Box 298, Folder 2221)
    - Museums - Denver Art Museum, 1974-1975 (Box 298, Folder 2222)
    - Museums - Exploratorium, 1976 (Box 298, Folder 2223)
    - Museums - Guggenheim Museum, 1971-1972 (Box 298, Folder 2224)
    - Museums - Indianapolis Museum of Art, 1976 (Box 298, Folder 2225)
    - Museums - Kimball Art Museum, 1972 (Box 298, Folder 2226)
    - Museums - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1970-1976 (Box 298, Folder 2227)
    - Museums - Museum of Modern Art, 1967-1975 (Box 298, Folder 2228)
    - Museums - New Muse, 1974 (Box 299, Folder 2229)
    - Museums - New York Jazz Museum, 1974 (Box 299, Folder 2230)
    - Museums - Old Sturbridge Village, 1976-1977 (Box 299, Folder 2231)
    - Museums - Pasadena Art Museum, 1976 (Box 299, Folder 2232)
    - Museums - Textile Museum, 1976 (Box 299, Folder 2233)
    - Museums - Toledo Museum of Art - Correspondence, 1970-1972; 1977 (Box 299, Folder 2234)
    - Museums - Toledo Museum of Art - Publications, 1973-1977 (Box 299, Folder 2235)
    - Museums - Wadsworth Atheneum, 1975 (Box 299, Folder 2236)
    - Museums - Whitney Museum, 1971; 1977 (Box 299, Folder 2237)
    - Urban Development Organizations - Agricultural Development Council, 1972-1973 (Box 299, Folder 2238)
    - Urban Development Organizations - Experimental Cities, 1975 (Box 299, Folder 2239)
    - Urban Development Organizations - Greater Jamaica Development Corporation, 1971-1976 (Box 299, Folder 2240)
    - Urban Development Organizations - Long Island Arts Study Committee, 1971 (Box 299, Folder 2241)
    - Urban Development Organizations - National Center for Urban Ethnic Affairs, 1973-1975 (Box 300, Folder 2242)
    - Urban Development Organizations - Pittsburgh Model Cities Program, 1971 (Box 300, Folder 2243)
    - Urban Development Organizations - Urban Development Corporation, 1971-1976 (Box 300, Folder 2244)
    - Urban Development Organizations - Urban Research Corporation, 1970-1972; 1975 (Box 300, Folder 2245)
    - Urban Development Organizations - Waterloo Recreation Commission, 1971 (Box 300, Folder 2246)
    - Miscellany - Miscellaneous Organizations, 1970; 1974 (Box 300, Folder 2247)
    - Miscellany - Instructional Materials - Correspondence, 1968-1973 (Box 300, Folder 2248)
    - Miscellany - Instructional Materials - "Good Examples", 1973-1975 (Box 300, Folder 2249)
    - Miscellany - Instructional Materials - Teaching Resource Materials, 1969-1972 (Box 300, Folder 2250)
    - Miscellany - Instructional Materials - Visual Literacy Materials - Eastman Kodak, 1969 (Box 300, Folder 2251)
    - Slides - Whitney Museum, n.d.; 15 slides; photograph (Box S 002, Folder 8)
      See also Box 299, Folder 2237
- General Records, 1963-1977; 12; 2.5 Cubic Feet 5 document cases
  This series consists of published annual reports and internal records of the JDR 3rd Fund (dockets, minute books, and organization book).
  - Annual Reports, 1963-1969 (Box 301, Folder 2252)
  - Annual Reports, 1970-1972 (Box 301, Folder 2253)
  - Annual Reports, 1973-1975 (Box 301, Folder 2254)
  - Annual Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 301, Folder 2255)
  - Dockets - Volume I, 1964-1965 (Box 301, Folder 2256)
  - Dockets - Volume II, 1965-1966 (Box 301, Folder 2257)
  - Dockets - Volume III, 1968-1969 (Box 302, Folder 2258)
  - Dockets - Volume IV, 1970-1971 (Box 302, Folder 2259)
  - Dockets - Volume V, 1972-1973 (Box 302, Folder 2260)
  - Dockets - Volume VI, 1973-1974 (Box 303, Folder 2261)
  - Dockets - Volume VII, 1975-1976 (Box 303, Folder 2262)
  - Minutes - Volume I, 1963-1964 (Box 303, Folder 2263)
  - Minutes - Volume II, 1965-1968 (Box 304, Folder 2264)
  - Minutes - Volume III, 1968-1972 (Box 304, Folder 2265)
  - Minutes - Volume IV, 1973-1974 (Box 304, Folder 2266)
  - Organization Book - Volume I, 1964 (Box 305, Folder 2267)
  - Organization Book - Volume II, 1964 (Box 305, Folder 2268)
- Miscellaneous Files, 1961-1985; 13; 0.5 Cubic Feet 1 document case
  - The American Federation of Arts, 1980 (Box 306, Folder 2269)
  - Arts in Education Program Staff, 1968-1979 (Box 306, Folder 2270)
  - Bassett Hall, 1979 (Box 306, Folder 2271)
  - Donations to JDR 3rd Fund with Condolence Letters, 1978 (Box 306, Folder 2272)
  - "Fine Arts Market Place" - Publication, 1977 (Box 306, Folder 2273)
  - Investment Advice, 1979-1985 (Box 306, Folder 2274)
  - National Council on Philanthropy, 1976-1977 (Box 306, Folder 2275)
  - Notification of Address Change and Termination of Service, 1979 (Box 306, Folder 2276)
  - Publication - JDR Memorial Service, Riverhead Church, 1978 (Box 306, Folder 2277)
  - Annual Report, 1968-1982 (Box 306, Folder 2278)
  - Annual Report and IRS Form 990-AR, 1978 (Box 306, Folder 2279)
  - 12-Year Report, 1977-1983 (Box 306, Folder 2280)
  - Expenditure Responsibility, 1970-1977 (Box 306, Folder 2281)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Leases, 1965-1980 (Box 306, Folder 2282)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - General, 1973-1980 (Box 306, Folder 2283)
  - Tax Status IRS Ruling - JDR 3rd Fund Inc., 1961-1973 (Box 306, Folder 2284)
  - JDR 3rd Fund Inc. - Financial Statements and Supporting Schedules, 1982-1983 (Box 306, Folder 2285)
  - Slides - Miscellany, 65 slides; photographs (Box S 2, Folder 9)
  - Slides - Miscellany, 257 slides; photographs (Box S 3, Folder 10)
- JDR 3rd Fund Annual Reports, 1970, 1973-1978; 14; 7 Bound Volumes
  Related Materials
  Additional annual reports can be found in Series 12: General Records.
  Annual reports
  - JDR 3rd Fund Annual Report 1970 (Item REF 361.74 JOH 1970)
  - JDR 3rd Fund Annual Report 1973 (Item REF 361.74 JOH 1973)
  - JDR 3rd Fund Annual Report 1974 (Item REF 361.7 HOH 1974)
  - JDR 3rd Fund Annual Report 1975 (Item REF 361.7 JOH 1975)
  - JDR 3rd Fund Annual Report 1976 (Item REF 361.74 JOH 1976)
  - JDR 3rd Fund Annual Report 1977 (Item REF 361.74 JOH 1977)
  - JDR 3rd Fund Annual Report 1978 (Item REF 361.74 JOH 1978)
- JDR 3rd Fund photographs, 1968-1977; 1040
  Photographs
  - Youth Task Force - General Correspondence - Harlem Youth Foundation, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 197)
  - Youth Task Force - Publications - National Dialog Conference, Palo Alto, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 198)
  - International Secretariat for Volunteer Services - 1968 Report (Box 15, Folder 199)
  - English Language Teaching in Japan - Committee for Cooperation on English in Japan, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 200)
  - Asian Cultural Program - Sumiko Kiyocka, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 201)
  - Asian Cultural Program - Miscellaneous Photos, 1969-1974 (Box 15, Folder 202)
  - Arts in Education - Jane Remer - Seven Loaves Network, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 203)
  - Arts in Education - Jane Remer - New York Project, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 204)
  - Arts in Education - Jane Remer - Little Rock, September 1975 (Box 15, Folder 205)
  - Arts in Education - Jane Remer - Minneapolis - Site Visit, November 11, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 206)
  - Arts in Education - Jane Remer - Minneapolis - Site Visit, 1977 October (Box 15, Folder 207)
  - Arts in Education - Jane Remer - New York City - Site Visit, 1977 May 13 (Box 15, Folder 208)
  - Arts in Education - Jane Remer - City Center's Young People's Theatre - Showboat, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 209)
  - Arts in Education - Kathryn Bloom - Annual Report, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 210)
  - Arts in Education - Kathryn Bloom - Annual Reports, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 211)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Annual Report, Project Photos, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 212)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Annual Report, Project Photos, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 213)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Annual Report, Project Photos, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 214)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Annual Report, Project Photos, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 215)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Annual Report, Project Photos, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 216)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Annual Report, Projects, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 217)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Annual Report, Projects, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 218)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Annual Report, Project Photos, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 219)